In a moment, I will show you a icon.
This icon is a screenshot of the tools or functions in Marvelous Designer.
When you correctly answer its full name in the first comment, you can get our prize.
Our prize is the right to use Marvelous Designer's personal license for one year.
This is our first prize.
Are you ready?
If you are, I will show you the first icon.
Okay.
Let's get started.
Let me see what icon I found first.
Okay, I'm ready.
The first prize is a screenshot of the tools or functions in Marvelous Designer.
There are three icons in total.
Okay.
The first icon is a screenshot of the tools or functions in Marvelous Designer's personal license for one year.
What is the name of this icon?
I have a method to search for the right name for this icon.
And I can easily find the –
I can deliberately look up the webpage.
I can see some documents made with this icon but the ID name is not the full name.
Let's see some posts and see if there are greater terms.
There are a hundred here.
They are very close.
What kind of Chinese name is it?
Oh! I've already seen it!
Okay.
Hou Guoyu Xun Qing Ji
Congratulations on winning the Marvelous Designer 1st prize
I will record your name later
Hou Guoyu Xun Qing Ji
Okay
Okay, this is our first icon
Okay, it's called Smart Top
Smart Top
It looks very similar to Editor Top
But it's a little pudding
So remember
You have to answer it in Chinese later
Okay
Let's look for the second icon
Hou Guoyu Xun Qing Ji
We've already won the prize
Remember to text us later
Or I will open the official account
Or I will open the official account to contact you next Sunday
I will contact you next Sunday
Okay?
I'm...
Okay, okay
Okay, this is a relatively simple one
Everyone, answer it quickly
I've already talked about this function many times
Okay, I see it
JoeyBanda000
Congratulations
Look at our long live broadcast
There are many interactions
I didn't expect you to answer it first
Folding Arrangement Tool
Okay
Congratulations, JoeyBanda000
It's called Folding Arrangement Tool
So we have...
There's one more tool
Let me think
Do you want it to be simpler or harder?
I have three options for you
It's okay
You have a second prize
for the guys who don't win the first prize
You can participate in the second prize
The second prize is Mr. Xu Kezheng,
the owner of Marvinuess Designer,
which is six months old
Okay
Oh, and all the winners will have a set of our secret prizes.
I'll tell you later when we text each other.
You want it to be a little harder, don't you?
Okay, I'll find one.
It doesn't seem that hard.
Let's do this.
It has a few brothers and sisters that look very similar to it.
What is this function called?
You have to say its full name.
Okay, I see it.
Consistency.
On the surface of the thick text.
That's right.
Its full name is...
Consistency.
On the surface of the thick text.
There are many friends who say,
Oh, I'm in Marvelous Designer.
How is the thickness set?
There is no difference.
That's because you didn't turn on the thick text surface.
On the surface of the thick text,
We have to be here in Marvelous Designer.
Change it from the text surface to the thick text surface.
Only then can you see its thickness.
Congratulations to these three friends.
Hou Guoyu, Xing Qingji, Joy, Banda, Lin Linlin and Yi Zhi.
These three friends have won the first prize.
The first prize is the right to use Marvelous Designer for a year.
Okay.
Let's take a look at the second prize.
Yes.
Our second prize draw rules.
There are also three second prize winners.
We will have three friends.
Get half a year of Marvelous Designer.
The right to use the personal version of the license.
I'll open the project file later.
The first to guess the characteristics of this item.
The audience can get a second prize.
The first prize is the item.
The characteristics of the item.
It may be various characteristics.
For example, its color.
For example.
Its...
Some...
Value.
Right.
The characteristics of the item.
Okay.
Let's get the first one first.
Wait a minute.
The first one to guess the characteristics of this item.
Will get the license of Marvelous Designer for half a year.
Okay.
You can guess what I'm going to ask.
This is the last package I made.
Okay.
We have a package.
You can see this package.
Okay.
Next, I'm going to ask.
This package.
It has a name.
What is the color of the name?
It's not red.
It's not green.
It's not yellow.
It's not white.
It's not brown.
Okay, I saw it.
Congratulations to Chen Weihuang.
Because the theme color of Marvelous Designer is orange.
So.
The color of the outline in this package is orange.
Okay.
Let's congratulate our friends just now.
The first one who says orange is a friend from the wilderness. Congratulations to you for becoming a wilderness. You will get a 6-month Marvelous Design license.
That's our draw. Now everyone knows how to draw the second prize, right?
Okay, let's move on to the next one.
Yes, isn't it fun?
Let's move on to this document.
This document is the one we showed you in the first part of the tutorial.
It shows you how to make a bag.
This bag has all kinds of colors.
We need to ask you this question.
Among the Marvelous Designers, what is the number of particles in the final version?
In the Marvelous Designers,
what is the number of particles in the final version?
Okay, I've already seen it.
There's a friend from the wilderness.
That's right.
The final version of Marvelous Designers is 20.
Congratulations.
Next, we're going to combine the first two questions.
Okay.
We often ask questions in the usual questions section.
For example, this year.
Let's talk about why there will be a draw.
Because we've organized a lot of questions all year round.
The draw section has a little bit of a relationship with the questions we usually ask.
Among the Marvelous Designers, our default particle interval is 20.
So sometimes there will be a problem.
You will find that after the model is imported,
it will look like my model is very large or very small.
Because the default particle interval is 20.
If your unit is wrongly imported,
will this model not match the version?
So our next question is.
Oops.
I haven't asked the question yet.
It's like this.
This is a virtual model that I imported from another software.
This virtual model has its own proportion.
Okay.
You have to wait for me to finish the question.
Then I will now import it into the default unit of Marvelous Designer.
We all know that Marvelous Designer is a default millimeter unit when you import OBJ.
After I import it in, this model becomes very small.
Originally, it would be different in size from our gift box.
But now it can fit into our gift box just right.
So,
In Marvelous Designer,
what is the default particle interval of the virtual model?
Oh.
I don't know.
Congratulations to Cryst certificate.
Is it?
Let me take a look.
esté http://www.anny.cryst.com
Is it?
I it seems that I was watching the sunset broadcast.
At script software, the default picture of the entire visual model is 3.
So, when we import the machine model to the wrong unit,
For example,
Formula Tw aquiван is hits,
For example, the software you originally used, its unit is mm, or mm is the opposite, for example, it is mm.
Because Marvelous Designer is a unit of mm when you import it directly, it should be a object with a height of 10 mm, or a character with a height of 165 mm.
If you import mm, it becomes only 16 mm high.
If you import mm, it becomes 20 mm, and if you import mm, it becomes 3 mm.
In this case, your model will look very large.
For example, I draw a model with the size of this virtual model.
In this case, the model is 20 mm.
Let's take a look.
Its network grid is very small.
In this case, the model is 20 mm.
In the case of a small network, a lot of triangles will appear in the figure.
So when we import into Marvelous Designer, we must pay attention.
First, is the unit right?
Second, because our default values ​​are all relatively large, for example, the surface diameter is 3 mm.
This surface diameter will make the virtual model look very small.
The thickness of the air will be thick, and you will feel that the fabric is not as thick as the air between the model and the model.
In fact, you have to pay attention to whether your unit is wrong.
Our second prize, the three little friends have already drawn it.
I want to record the names of our three little friends.
The winners of the second prize are Chen Weihuangye, Bingjiezhiban, and Xiyangxiang.
Don't change your BB name.
Otherwise, we may not be able to find you.
I accidentally sent it to someone who is the same age as you.
Now let's talk about the three prizes.
The three prizes are actually very simple.
Wait a minute, I'll give you an instruction.
When the countdown is over, the last comment on the chat will be the prize of the three prizes.
The chat will be displayed and placed next to the live interaction.
I will count down three times.
The last comment will be the prize of the three prizes.
The prize is the prize of the Bilibili Conference.
There are three people in total.
I will think of an instruction first.
The first instruction is that the GPU simulation is easy to use.
However, the GPU simulation is not easy to use.
Everyone can start now.
The GPU simulation is easy to use.
I will count down later.
I want to see everyone type out the GPU simulation is easy to use.
I have already won the first and second prize.
I can't participate in the lottery.
The GPU simulation is easy to use.
I will count down 5 4 3 2 1.
5 4 3 2 1
Don't kill me first
I will think of a code name later
What code name should I think of?
Happy New Year
I will count down later
I also want to click
screenshot
But I didn't turn on QQ
Happy New Year
Ok
I will use screenshot later
I will try
screenshot first
Ok
I can use screenshot now
I will
screenshot later
Ok
I will count down
5 4 3
2 1
Happy New Year
Let's see who is the last
Ok
I can see
The last one is
Ok
Congratulation
Why is your name so funny?
Ok
You don't need to screenshot
The last one
Ok
In the bottom left corner of the screen
There is a
The latest version of Marvelous Designer
Please
Call 139
End
024.2.139
I will count down
5 4 3 2 1
End
2024.2.139
1964.2.139
End
Stop
Said
Okay, let's see which one is the lucky audience.
Wait a minute, I'll put this
The
year-end lottery is over here.
Let's congratulate the little friend who just won the lottery.
I remember there was a little friend who was CHOUDO, right?
Let's record the little friend who won the prize.
Thank you for your support for Marvelous Designer once a year.
If you especially like us to hold such an event,
be sure to leave a message under our video or dynamic.
Because we are about to have the Spring Festival.
Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry.
We're about to have the Spring Festival, right?
Thank you for your support once a year.
I hope that in the new year,
Marvelous Designer will be able to
accompany you more.
If you like us to hold such an interesting event,
you can also learn some small knowledge activities.
Don't forget to leave us a message.
Thank you for your support all the time.
I'm Xuanyi.
See you in the next video.
See you in the next live broadcast.
Thank you for your support.
Goodbye, everyone.
Good night.
Have a good rest.
Happy New Year.
Good night, everyone.
Bye bye.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, everyone.
Okay.
Happy New Year.
Thank you for your support.
Good night.
Bye bye.
Goodbye.
Thank you for your support.